TANJRO, LOOK OUT!
Damn it!
Zenichu, forget about me!
This happened because I wasn't paying attention.
I'm sorry, Inosuke.
If only I'd noticed him sooner than maybe...
No.
If I hadn't left Mr. Uzui's side in the first place, this never would have happened.
It's my fault.
I'm sorry, everyone.
Please forgive me.
launches a single point.
is
a little too
Thank you.
There's nothing for you to be sorry for.
Big brother, why do you always apologize?
If we're poor and can't afford to wear nice kimonos, is that something you have to be sorry for?
Don't blame yourself for something like that.
It would be like blaming father for succumbing to his illness.
He tried as hard as he could, but it wasn't enough.
We have to accept that.
We're human after all, and part of that means there are things that are outside of our control.
Whether I'm happy or not is up to me, even if it feels like the world is against me.
What's most important is that we keep moving forward together, and fight if we must.
So stop apologizing.
You of all people should understand.
I want you to understand how I feel.
Was that a dream about the past?
Hold on.
Where am I?
Am I...
This is awful.
How did it come to this?
I just hope the people who lived here were able to escape.
Nezuko!
Nezuko...
Thank you, Nezuko.
My fault or not, I've got to do what I can do.
Well, I'm impressed.
I'm shocked you're still alive after that.
You're one lucky guy, aren't you?
Well, not that you have anything going for you, except being lucky, that is.
It really is a shame, you know.
Every one of your friends is dead or burning under the rubble right now.
It only took a single thrust to that boar's heart.
Meanwhile, that yellow-haired boy is trapped under the rubble, so I think I'll leave him there
until he dies, squirming around like an insect.
How disgraceful is that?
And that Hashira...
He really was all bark and no bite.
It seems the poison got to him after all, and now he's dead like the others.
You're all disgraceful.
Utterly disgraceful.
You all might be pathetic and shameless in your own ways, but you're by far the worst!
By far the worst!
The one sticking out of that box.
That's a relative of yours, isn't it?
I can tell she's related to you, you know, even if she is a demon.
Tell me, who is she, your younger sister?
Why won't he kill me?
What's going on here?
My arm is numb.
I couldn't lift my sword if I wanted to.
So if I went for his head now, I couldn't slash it.
The girl in the box... is my younger sister.
It's just as I thought then.
You really are a disgrace, huh?
Imagine being so useless you can't protect your own sister.
Well, I guess it can't be helped.
After all, you're just human.
It makes sense you're weaker than your sister.
Considering she's a demon, it only makes sense she's stronger than you.
Even so, I just can't help but see you as a disgrace.
If you're really her big brother, then you should be protecting her instead of leaving her to fight all of your battles for you, you coward.
Devotedly.
With this hand, you see?
But I've got to know, how do you feel after all this?
Being the only one to survive so disgracefully.
Not to mention you let that kid sister of yours use up her strength protecting a disgrace like you.
Hey, answer me, worm.
You imbecile.
Sad sack.
Coward.
Good for nothing.
Why was trash like you even born to begin with?
What are you gonna do?
I don't know about you, but I'd love to see you try and cut off my head with that useless, battered, disgraceful human body of yours.
Come on!
Oh, I see. Your poor little soul got crushed at the last second, huh?
How disgraceful are you? I didn't think you could get more pathetic.
I gotta hand it to you. You really are the most disgraceful scumbag.
In all my life, I've never seen anyone as shameless or cowardly as you.
Oh, I can't help you.
Anything that's pathetic, disgraceful, and filthy, you understand?
What is it about you? Maybe it's this filthy scar on your forehead I'm getting attached to.
I have an idea. How about you just become a demon, too?
Why not do it for your little sister's sake? Oh, why couldn't I have thought of that sooner?
If you become a demon, I'll spare your life, since you and I will be comrades then.
Otherwise, I'll slaughter you and your pathetic sister, since I don't give a crap about other people's little sisters, to be honest.
No way! Absolutely not, brother! I am not on board with this, understand?
And if you become a demon, you can instantly become stronger!
You can kiss that defective body of yours goodbye!
So what do you say? What's it gonna be?
It makes you bitter, huh? Realizing how weak you are.
Humans are so cute, looking to the sky when you grieve.
All so you don't let your tears fall down your face.
This whole time...
I've been waiting for this!
You've been waiting for a pathetic last-ditch headbutt!
My body won't...
What are you doing, brother? Get back up on your feet!
Something's wrong. What's going on? Something's wrong!
All he did was use a lame headbutt!
A kunai? I got stabbed when he headbutted me!
He was pretending to retreat when he was really going for this kunai!
All the while scattering the courtesan sachets to cover up the scent of the kunai's poison!
Damn you! Damn you!
You're still a rotten weakling of a human!
Look how bruised and battered you are even after taking me on with three others helping you!
But now you're alone, so why?
Why won't you give up?
Why is it you're so damn determined...
To decapitate me?
AHHHHHHHHHH!!!
Brother...brother...
Big Brother!
Brother!
At every turn, one false step and I could have found myself in the very same situation he's in right now.
I was lucky enough to remain a human.
But there could have been a future in which we were both demons.
If I do end up turning into a demon, I know I can rely on one thing.
That someone in the Demon Slayer Corps will behead me for the greater good.
Cut through! Cut through!
Win! Win! No matter what!
We're going to win!
Hey! What the hell are you doing?
Don't get beheaded by someone like him!
That brat. He pulled himself out of the rubble.
Die, you ugly freak!
Thunder breathing. First form.
Luckily, I know exactly how fast your move is because I've seen it so many times now!
Thunderclap and Flash.
Godlike Speed!
So fast!
My head's being severed!
Damn it. I had no idea he could move like this!
Cut through! Cut through her!
My body can only handle using Thunderclap and Flash Godlike Speed twice!
And I've already used it once to escape the rubble!
I won't get another chance to go over her neck if I don't do it now!
Tanjiro created this one in a million chance!
I'm going to slash her for sure!
No matter what!
Damn it! It's no use!
I can't cut through!
The poison should have weakened him!
Am I still not strong enough?
He's recovered from the poison!
His blades are engulfing me!
And my sword! It's being repelled!
Damn it! I almost had him there!
Just a few more seconds and I could've...
Don't give up! Don't give up, Tanjiro!
Hang on until the very end!
Die, you little punch!
His attack speed is increasing!
He's broken down the poison and fully recovered!
But don't give up!
Don't give up!
He's not dead!
But how is that possible?
Wait! His heart!
I get it!
He used his muscles to stop his heart!
Which stopped the poison from circulating!
Mr. Ozu-weep!
My musical score technique will take us to victory!
Don't make me laugh!
Michi!
Uh-huh!
Oh!
This is a joke!
Eat!
I can read it now!
That filthy musical score of yours!
He deflected my rotating circular slashes!
Amazing!
Wait!
Did he say score?
He turned my blood demon art into a song and deflected it!
And he did it all using only one arm!
There's no way that's possible!
I've had enough of your trap!
Oh, my goodness!
He might be holding his own right now, but that's not enough to beat him.
Mr. Uzo is going to reach his limit first.
I've got to make a move before that happens.
If I can decapitate him, victory is ours!
Mr. Uzo-A, don't stop!
Stop!
Unfortunately, you're too slow!
He paved the way for you and you still blew your chance!
It's over. The poison will kill you!
Even if it costs my life, I will behead you!
I won't give up. I'm cutting your head off no matter what!
Damn you! What's it going to take for you to give up?
You couldn't behead me before. What makes you think you can now?
I can't just use my arms. I've got to use every ounce of strength I have!
From the top of my head to the tips of my toes!
I have to ignore all the pain in my body. Endure!
Striking with all my might won't be enough!
I need one hundred time supports! Summon every ounce of strength left!
Damn it! Not by a brat like him!
If I don't do something, I'm gonna get beheaded!
No, it's fine. Even if I get beheaded.
As long as my sister's head is still intact!
And I can finish off this stubborn punk!
Damn it! I'm running out of strength!
It's too bad you'll never get the chance to decapitate me!
Because before you do, I'm gonna tear you to shreds!
What's he doing here? Doesn't Brother impale him through the heart?
Don't underestimate the sheer flexibility of my body!
Shifting the position of my internal organs is nothing but child play for me!
And since I grew up on the harsh mountainside,
poison doesn't work on me either!
Help me, Brother!
Do something before I get decapitating!
I need to unleash the rotating circulatory slashes!
Oh!
Yeah!
Oh! Oh!
Oh!
They did it.
They really did it.
They did it!
Hear that, Hinatsu?
Just take a look for me on the grave!
What the?
Do you even know what you're saying to her?
What?
Dummy!
That hurt!
Hold on a second.
Something's not right here.
The poison.
Use your breathing to combat it.
S-Slow down the poison.
As much as you can.
What?
What is he saying?
Does it mean...
I didn't cut off his head?
Mr. Uzui is...
Saying something.
You gotta run.
What?
No.
Oh, my God.
Oh, yeah.
Thank you.
When I was still just a little girl, I heard that Mother was able to repel a boar all by herself by headbutting him.
Next, the final episode, no matter how many lives.
You've got this, brother.
I know you have what it takes to win.